With supplies being limited,
we'll need to add a rule allowing
passage in and out of the colony.
But I can't afford to let players like
Dhruv, who attack people indiscriminately,
leave the barriers.
I should wait until the players like him
are eliminated from the
other colonies first.
Communication between colonies is a must.
There's the two rules Fushiguro proposed,
a means of communication and
passage in and out of the colonies.
So we'll need four additional rules
to get the situation under control?
Everyone's still at their physical
and emotional limit from Shibuya.
Gojo, I won't let you kill
your best friend twice!
I'll kill Kenjaku myself.
I'll get the 400 points on my own
Okay, you can all come out now.
I think we should continue making our
way north to the edge of the barrier.
Can you carry me?
Just hang in there, sweetheart.
Why don't we take a quick rest?
We're safe here.
This stadium was being controlled
by the sorcerer I just defeated.
Any player that comes along
will be pretty hesitant to...
What's that sound?
Quick, get into the stadium. Let's go!
Let's get out of here!
Hurry up.
No!
No! No!
Are these cockroaches real?
Rika, knock it down! Hurry!
Kogane, is that a player?
Yes, that is a player called Kuro Arushi.
So some players are cursed spirits.
I'm being watched.
Likely, it's the other two
players with high points.
Why do you interfere?
Kuro Urushi is a cursed spirit.
Why do you kill us?
I can exercise it.
I just have to drive positive energy from
my reverse curse technique into its body.
I can ask you the same question, but...
Because I like the taste of Naira!
I don't want those other two players to
know I can use reverse curse technique.
Rika is protecting
everyone in the stadium,
so I have to exercise Kuro Urushi without
using Rika or my reverse curse technique.
Blinding! Blinding! Blinding!
Hmph!
Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Uh... Ah! Uh...
Uh...
Ah! Ah! Amai!
You have gained five points for a kill.
I see that you can use.
Reverse Cursed Technique.
What was that? A strike?
My arm is back to normal.
I feel fine.
Her technique probably manipulates space.
But I guess she can't use that
space to crush her opponents.
It seems to create distortions
like a funhouse mirror.
You're wondering about my technique.
It treats the sky as a surface.
Here let me show you.
She's revealing her technique.
Hurry up and attack already.
I have to ask.
You're not someone who's going to
complain about getting killed, are you?
I mean I can understand powerless
people getting desperate for points.
But a strong person like you can
claim points whenever they want.
So what's your reason for
actively seeking a fight?
This little brat seriously are you?
Modern day sorcerers that
casual about incarnation?
To us from the old school.
This means coming back from the dead.
People who lived out their lives without
regrets wouldn't accept Kenjaku's offer,
would they?
He's really pissing me off.
I like to think of the culling game as the
first step toward a
chance at a second life.
Keep in mind that Kenjaku
set the stage for this.
Anything could happen.
We need to?
to earn points to prepare ourselves.
I wonder if someone like you
has any friends or lovers.
Huh?
You know what?
Until recently, I didn't
have any friends either.
Not that I feel sorry for you.
This feeling, it's like he's
hunting for things that trigger me.
Your pain was caused
thousands of years ago.
The people alive today have
nothing to do with your regrets.
How many have to die until
you finally feel avenged?
Wait just a minute.
Are you one of the Fujiwara?
How can anyone from your
bloodline understand me?
Granite blast.
Ishigori?
It came from that rooftop.
Too close for comfort.
Even with Rika protecting the stadium, a
direct hit from an attack on that level?
will leave several people dead.
So I have to take Ishigori out first.
Now that Code Urushi and Dhruv are gone,
I have no reason to let Ishigori run free.
I'll take both him and Okotsu out.
Brennan Blast!
Come on, don't disappoint me.
He's gone.
No, that's where Akotsu
dug a hole earlier.
Can't you fight without blowing
up everything around you?
Oh, but that won't
satisfy my hunger, Okotsu.
Would you tell a starving
kid with a feast in
front of him to take
his time and eat slower?
Wouldn't anyone?
I guess so.
Most probably would.
That was a bad example.
My first run at life was in
completely lacking flavor.
Some of the guys I
fought had real backbone.
I even met a nice woman, too.
Frankly, it'd be hard to say
I had any regrets at all.
This vague hunger I constantly feel
is always gnawing at me, Okotsu.
Everyone's always wondering
what I'm so unsatisfied about.
These cigarettes have a
slightly sweet aftertaste.
You know what it was?
There was no dessert in my life.
Here it comes!
Why am I unsatisfied I think you know?
I'm unsatisfied because I'm not fulfilled.
You better not be crushed.
Hey, what's the hair?
Nice!
Not calling you a Shikigami?
I can't right now.
Not with you going wild.
Oh, that's a shame.
He's probably trying to
limit where I can go.
But I'll break through.
Head on!
Sweet!
That's it, Akutsu!
Keep on coming!
This cursed energy!
So precise!
Here's your reward.
Uh-oh.
I overheated my hand.
You're good, Oko-choo.
Could you be the one?
Are you my dessert?
You're great!
Best I've seen so far!
What I strike isn't the person,
but the surface of the sky.
Thin icebreaker!
Get lost, you pile of vomit!
Shut your mouth, dick cheese!
This guy's resilient.
Glad you're alive.
I wanted to torment you some more.
What a hit.
That was the first time I've been
forced to eat my old technique.
Reverse Cursed Technique
is a pain to deal with,
but it burns Cursed Energy like crazy.
We're finally seeing the bottom
of your reserves, Okotsu.
No matter how high end the sweet shop is,
seeing the displays empty at closing
time is always disappointing.
Guess it wasn't you.
I wanted to gain more distance
from everyone in the stadium.
Keep them out of harm's way.
Oh well.
Come to me, Rika.
Give me everything!
Has Shikigami completely manifested?
How does that work?
Any swelling with cursed energy again?
Which would you like, Rika?
Thank you.
I'll take that one.
Rika is the stockpile of Cursed Energy and
the externalization of Okotsu's technique.
It remained with him after
Rika Orimoto passed on.
While connected to Rika through
the ring, he gains the following.
Use of his Cursed Technique,
the complete manifestation of Rika,
and the Cursed Energy supplied by Rika.
Yuta can remain connected
to Rika for five minutes.
Okay, let's go.
Don't underestimate me.
Don't move.
Snake eyes and fangs.
I can't move.
Oh, man.
You are super sweet, huh?
Rika.
Rage! Yeah!
Oh, no!
That was close.
You can't get rid of me that easy!
Help me! You!
You hurt Yaga!
What now?
Let's go!
Even with this, I can't fully block it.
Wanna go?
Uh!
Huh?
Finn, icebreaker!
Fujiwara!
I've still got a strong appetite!
Let's keep chowing down!
It's always you, Fujiwara.
You're always getting in my way.
Are you that afraid of me?
Afraid of me becoming my own person?
Okotsu defeated Drew Vlaktawala,
whose technique made the path of
his Shikigami into his domain?
which cut into anything it touched.
This is Dhruv's technique.
Does that mean Bakotsu's
technique is copy?
I don't know what my ancestors did to
you, but that has nothing to do with me.
If you live only for your own sake, you're
eventually going to reach your limit.
Shut up.
Live for the sake of others?
You think I'll eventually reach my limit?
Stop barking those things at me!
It's easy for you to say
you've already become someone!
Quit your whining,
because at this point,
words are meaningless!
Don't leave expansion!
Future, give me back!
Even if it tries to
penetrate the barrier later!
I ain't gonna drag this out,
let's settle this nice and sweet!
At that moment, the black
devil of the modern age...
I told you, I like the taste of iron!
...flew into the barriers.
Kurourushi had completed
Parthenogenesis before going dormant.
So Kurourushi was still alive
and well as a cursed spirit.
The complex forces of their domains had
been keeping the three sorcerers in check.
But this intruder was unexpected,
and so the barriers collapsed.
How's Kuro Orushi still alive?
Damn, I can't use my technique
right after domain expansion.
How dare you take my arm? Fujiwara!
Enough, Uro. Quiet.
You and the roach were
never invited to my table.
Granite blast.
Ishigori's technique is
cursed energy discharge.
It's an extremely simple attack,
but it performs just as well, even
when his technique is burnt out.
Now...
Welcome to my table, Okotsu.
Rika, let's go.
Okotsu can discharge a high
volume of Cursed Energy,
but only while Rika is
completely manifested. However,
his maximum output is slightly
inferior to Ishigori's,
so he planned to charge
and unleash his Cursed
Energy before Ishigori
reached maximum output.
But he changed his mind.
400 years of longing.
The intense gaze full of that hunger.
Melted Yuta Okotsu's heart.
Even though he would likely
never find meaning In fighting.
Alright, just this once.
That was some seriously
sweet star for Konzu!
Yeah, atta boy!
Let's keep this dinner party going!
That big thing can fire on its
own, but its force is weak.
After domain expansion and a meal with me,
even you haven't had enough time to
digest and recover your full strength.
I'll end this granite blast!
But Okotsu's technique
had already recovered.
He's using Uro's technique.
I knew he was more than
just a cursed speech user.
And I figured that big thing probably had
a different technique from Okotsu's too.
So that's it.
Okotsu's technique is copy.
But there should be
strenuous conditions on it.
When did he satisfy those conditions?
While I wasn't looking?
Maybe there aren't any!
That was when he did it!
It's an icebreaker!
Five minutes.
Okotsu's connection to Rika was seven.
Is this the feeling?
There's still more after going all out!
This is what it's like to eat dessert.
We're done.
What?
What does he mean?
Was that my technique?
I see.
He sent it sailing back to
me using Hugo's technique.
Thank you, Oconso.
I'm full now.
Okotsu, you're too soft.
That's not a compliment.
Sparing the life of a sorcerer
who fought to kill you.
There's nothing to gain from killing you.
Uro told me the same thing.
You mean that woman's still alive?
Well, I guess my blast was
weaker after my domain expansion.
Hey, what was it she kept going on about?
Were you having a lover spat?
Yeah, something like that.
Eh, don't let her get to ya.
There's nothing I can say to
that woman to change her mind.
Anything I do say will lead to violence.
You see, it's because I'm blessed.
Is that how it works?
Because frankly, I don't get it.
Well, regardless, can I
have your points? Huh?
Now I get it.
So if we didn't give you our points,
you would have killed us, right?
I'm not so sure about that.
All I know is you should
be grateful to my friends.
You're the one who's
going to reach your limit.
I've seen it.
Be it sorcerer or cursed spirit.
All are driven over the
edge by the same thing.
Overwhelming aggression that
blinds them to everything else.
Like a calamity.
If I'm broken and broken,
I'll be able to die.
I'm not afraid of it.
I'm not
afraid
of it.